{
    "subject": "resource/ALARGAN_International_Real_Estate_Company",
    "predicate": "ontology/foundingYear",
    "object": "1994",
    "human_readable": "ALARGAN International Real Estate Company was founded in 1994.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9537971615791321,
            "question": "When was ALARGAN International Real Estate Company founded?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.850455641746521,
            "question": "Is ALARGAN International Real Estate Company a local or international company?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8122967481613159,
            "question": "In what year did ALARGAN International Real Estate Company begin operations?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7891342639923096,
            "question": "What type of company is ALARGAN International Real Estate Company?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7187232375144958,
            "question": "Where is ALARGAN International Real Estate Company headquartered?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6785154938697815,
            "question": "What does ALARGAN International Real Estate Company specialize in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6648280620574951,
            "question": "What industry does ALARGAN International Real Estate Company operate in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6369404792785645,
            "question": "What are some of the services offered by ALARGAN International Real Estate Company?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5983125567436218,
            "question": "How old is ALARGAN International Real Estate Company?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5185383558273315,
            "question": "Does ALARGAN International Real Estate Company have a website?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=ALARGAN International Real Estate Company was founded in 1994.",
            "html": "dbpedia_840_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How old is ALARGAN International Real Estate Company?",
            "html": "dbpedia_840_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some of the services offered by ALARGAN International Real Estate Company?",
            "html": "dbpedia_840_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What industry does ALARGAN International Real Estate Company operate in?",
            "html": "dbpedia_840_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_840_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_840_103.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_840_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_840_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_840_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_840_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_840_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_840_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_840_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_840_73.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple. The company's history and evolution, as mentioned in several files, confirm that Alargan International Real Estate Company was indeed established in 1994."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe information provided in the documents explicitly states that Alargan International Real Estate Company was established in 1994, thus supporting the given triple."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}